[{"answer": "How did you know", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Does Drew tell you everything", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Good morning, Quince", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm doing great.  You ready", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "And I'm your daughter and no man will ever be good enough for me", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What were you going to say", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Good morning, I was talking kind of loud there, sorry", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh yeah?  What was 'fascinating' about it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm sorry", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What's the way", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "'Yes' is the answer to your question", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I believe you did", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What do you mean?", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Know what?  Know what, goddammit", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Lunch is 'in' today, have you given it any thought", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Nothing", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "'The one' to do what", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Get what", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "We have an arrangement now", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I didn't say", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You act like you never had peanut butter before", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "-- What kind of childhood did you have", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Why yes, thank you", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Cold", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Of whom", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Then why did you bring it up", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You're not familiar with the phrase,", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Glad I could be of some help", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Very well, I'll watch", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Whatever you do", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Whatever you do", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "And I'll be a visitor", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I nuttin' to do wi' dat", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Doctor lady make it irey", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Make it go 'way", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Not dis pain.  Dis pain tru an' tru. Make it go 'way", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Excuse me", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "And I appreciate you, too", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Why do you love peanut butter so much", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I adore things like that....food I can't do without.  Don't you", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yes..", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Yes...I've found that it does", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "About my friend", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What way would you put it", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "my friend, you're out of line", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Sorry, but I like the way he looks and talks to me.  And vice versa. Okay", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Where are you going", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " 'To bed'", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Yeah, it's good to get together", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Raise away", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "How did my friend react to the leads you've developed", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " -- But he was concerned about the timing", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": " -- But he was concerned about the timing", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "'It's up to my friend'", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I don't like cake", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Oh, the goddam party", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "It's for the party, Dad", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "'Goddam party'", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": " Feel better", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "But what", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, my friend", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "What's okay", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "I am", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "She knows how she feel", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "She knows how she feel", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " my friend' need you okayin'", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Why are you giving me money", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I am who I am.  I cannot change", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": " Above all, you've been a wonderful father", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "That you've been to my friend", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "'Love'?  Oh, man, I've got troubles of my own", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Oh yes, I do", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "You love my friend, don't you", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "How did you meet", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": " How do you know", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "'The deepest, darkest secrets", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "I can tell you the when part.  Tonight", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "No worse than it gets for me.  I'm in love with a woman whom I don't want to leave", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "What will we do", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "'Love will find out the way'", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": " my friend went, in whatever way she did, for that poor sonofabitch whose body you took, and everything else since has been aftermath.  You say you love her but you don't know what love is. She 'loves' you but she doesn't know who you are.  You make a deal, you're breaking it", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "I don't expect you to", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": " You're a worthless sack of shit, you fucked me over, played footsie with my friend, sold my company out to line your own pockets", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "The Board didn't know you're a mole who burrowed inside so you could bury us all", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Undisclosed conflict of interest", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "An indictable offense", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": " Confess to the Board every details of your participation and then submit your resignation", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "You get not to go to jail", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "You get not to go to jail", "docId": "Meet-Joe-Black.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "Proof?  We've got plenty of proof", "qsentId": 90}]